&GT；&GT；Will Sentance：让我们谈谈好处和
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Let's
talk about the benefits and
而不是这种方法的好处。
not to benefits of this approach.
所以，问题99%的开发人员不知道这是如何在引擎盖下工作的，
So, problems 99% of developers have
no idea how this work under the hood,
这使得调试成为一件神秘的事情。
which makes debugging
just this mystery thing.
最重要的是，我想是的，我现在说了，
And on top of that,
I think yeah, I said that now,
最重要的是，我感觉要去面试了。
on top of that I felt going to interviews.
这种风格的好处是它创造了某种意味着
The upside of this style is it
creates something that sort of means
如果你不明白它是如何工作的，你可以大致让它起作用。
if you don't understand how it's working,
you can roughly make it kind of work.
我要说的是旧的风格，你可以直接传递一个函数，
I will say about the old style where
you literally pass a function in,
如果你明白它是怎么工作的。
if you understand how it's working.
你有点完蛋了，这种风格，因为这种外观，
You're kinda done, this style,
because of this appearance,
当时的方法，你觉得你知道它在做什么，它是一种工作，但是
the then method you kind of think you know
what it's doing and it kind of work but
真的，我讨厌这个名字。
really, I hate this name, then.
它什么都不做，如果我作为开发人员阅读这些代码，我会说，好的，所以
It's doing nothing, if I'm reading this
code as a developer I'm like, okay, so
拿来然后我要展示。
fetching and then I'm gonna display.
但当然，这还不够，
But of course, it's not even close,
也许我们甚至会这样想，如果我们回到这条线上，做那一行
maybe we even think that kind of if we go
back up the thread and do that line and
然后再点，不，那么应该改名什么？
then bit later, No, no, no,
then should be renamed what?
我认为它应该重命名为这个，存储函数以后运行，是的，没错。
I think it should be renamed this, store
function to Run later, yeah, exactly.
将来日期点，存储我以后自动运行我的后台任务
Future dated dot, store me to Run me later
automatically when the background task
先前从fetch调用中出来的
that came out of the fetch
call previously completes and
值可能会被更新。
the value probably gets updated.
不是上口，但它是准确的，嗯哼，所以我会增加一个额外的好处，虽然。
Not catchy, but it is accurate, mm-hm,
so I will add one more benefit though.
所以人们认为这是一种更干净，更易读的风格，
So people think kind of cleaner,
readable style,
我会说，就像伪同步，
I will say, like pseudo synchronous,
它看起来像是你当时正在运行它，但你真的不是。
it sort of looks like you are running
it right then but you really are not.
您正在传递一个函数，该函数也将像以前一样运行，
You are passing in a function that
is going to be also run as before,
不是你，而是JavaScript。
not by you, but by JavaScript.
它接受了一个你没有放进去的输入，JavaScript放进去了。
And it's taking an input that you did not
put in there, JavaScript put in that.
从后台工作的高字符串将是自动的
That from the background work that
high string that's gonna be auto
当它自动运行时插入显示功能，我喜欢它。
inserted into display function
when it's AutoRun, I love it.
顺便说一下，一旦您看到JavaScript是
By the way,
once you see that JavaScript was
我们可以看到JavaScript正在使用显示的功能代码，并且
one sees that JavaScript is taking
that function code of display, and
它通过自动为你打印来为你运行它。
it's running it for you by putting
Print on it for you automatically.
它正在插入输入
And it's inserting the input for
从这个意义上说，你当然是一种非常慷慨的语言。
you automatically It's a very
generous language in that sense.
这种设计有一个很大的好处，并且
There is one big benefit of this design,
and
这是那个时代的处理过程，所以，这真的很好。
it's that era handling process,
so, this is really nice.
原来人们，实际上还有另一个
It turns out people,
there's actually another
幕后此Promise对象上的数组，这是另一个隐藏的属性。
array on this promise object behind
the scenes, another hidden property.
它被称为onRjection，它也是一个数组，我们可以将函数放入其中。
And it's called onRjection, and it's also
an array into which we can put functions.
尤其是当你和外面的世界互动的时候
When you're interacting with
the outside world especially
网络上的东西你总是会收到错误。
network stuff you get errors all the time.
你不想运行你的显示功能，所以Twitter上的用户会得到一个可爱的
You don't wanna run your display functions
so the user on Twitter gets a lovely
广播错误的全部细节。
broadcast of the full
details of the error.
理想情况下，希望有一个单独的函数来运行
Ideally wanna have a separate
function that's going to run
处理该错误的。
that handles that error.
也许它会以某种方式为你记录下来，但是
Maybe it logs it for you in some way, but
可能只是给用户更好的体验。
probably just gives the user
a better experience.
它正在做类似的事情，也许，不管是什么，
It's doing something similar,
maybe, whatever it might be,
现在，我们该怎么处理呢？
now, how can we handle that?
你知道吗？
Well, you know what?
Promise对象为我们提供了这一惊人功能，
The promise object give
us this amazing feature,
这意味着如果我们得到一个错误，而不是实际的响应对象，我们想要任何错误，
that means if we get an error back not the
actual response object we want any error,
它不会运行显示功能。
it's not gonna Run that display function.
它甚至不会自动触发你未完成的任何功能，
It's not even gonna auto trigger any
of your functions in unfulfilled,
它会触发你存储在onRejection中的任何函数
it's gonna trigger any functions
that you stored in onRejection,
我们如何在那里获得函数？
how do we get functions in there?
嗯，有两种方法，
Well, there's two ways,
一个是写未来，&gt；&gt；Will Sentance：数据点，有人知道吗？
one would be to write future,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Data dot, anyone know?
网点接点准确，凯特是对的，网点接点，和
Dot catch spot on exactly,
Cate is right, dot catch, and
我们在里面传递的任何函数，都会被拒绝，对吗？
any function we pass in there,
it's going on rejection, right?
另一种方式是暂停到THEN作为第二个参数，
The other way is to pause to
then as the second argument,
你想要的任何功能都会在这里出现错误时自动运行，
whatever function you want that's going
to go in here to AutoRun on error,
第一个参数，将该函数放在unfulled中。
first argument,
stick that function in unfulfilled.
然后我们将进行第二个论点，
Then we'll take the second argument,
第二个输入并保留您拒绝的功能？
the second input and
stay that function that you rejected?
那真的很好，这真的是，
That's really nice, that's a really,
毫无疑问，非常好的错误处理方法。
really nice error handling
approach without a doubt.
好了，伙计们，现在我们有了它，我们现在有了规则
Alright folks, so there we have it,
we now have rules for
我们的异步延迟代码的执行包含Promise延迟功能。
the execution of our asynchronously delay
code hold promise deferred functions.
这就是丹所说的承诺延期功能，
This is what Dan was saying
promise deferred functions,
那些与承诺相联系的人会推迟他们的运行
ones that were attached to
a promise to delay them running
直到后台发生了一些事情。
until something happened
in the background.
将它们存储在微任务队列和回调函数中，
Store them in the microtask queue and
callback functions,
传递给其中一个门面函数的函数，如计时器，对不起，
ones that were passed in to one of these
facade functions like timer, sorry,
设置超时，让它们进入回调队列。
set timeout,
have them go in the callback queue.
当网络浏览器特征否则存在API完成时，
When the web browser feature
otherwise there is API finishes,
将该函数添加到冷却堆栈。
add that function to the coolstack.
换句话说，当Coolstack为空时运行它，并且
In other words,
Run it when coolstack is empty and
所有全局代码都已完成运行，请让事件newcheck为我们检查此条件。
all global code is finished running, have
the event newcheck this condition for us.
在我们知道代码是我接下来会运行之前，
Before we learn the code
is I would Run next,
将微任务队列中的函数优先于回调队列。
prioritize functions in the microtask
queue over the callback queue.
承诺Web浏览器功能、回调和微任务队列以及
Promises web browser features,
the callback and microtask queues and
事件循环使我们能够构建非阻塞应用程序。
the event loop enable us to
build non blocking applications.
我们不必在这个JavaScript线程中等待，
We do not have to wait in this
single JavaScript thread,
我们不必在这里等待我们的数据回来。
we do not have to wait here for
our data to come back.
这条线上没有等待，FETCH不会坐在这条线上，等待
No waiting on this line, fetch will
not sit on this line, waiting for
要回来的数据，不。
the data to come back, no, no, no, no.
我的意思是不，在我们的常规代码中，
I mean no in regular code we do,
你的功能很酷，你一直呆在那条线上，直到你完成它。
your function cool you are staying
on that line till you finish it.
但它不是常规的函数调用，它是用于
But it is not a regular function call,
it is a facade function for
设置后台工作。
setting up background work.
无论需要多长时间，我们都无法预测浏览器的功能何时起作用
However long it takes we can't predict
when our browser's features work
将在后台完成。
will finish in the background.
我们不能确切地知道它什么时候结束，所以我们不能把线
We can't know exactly when it's gonna
finish, so we can't kind of have the line
使用背景数据的代码现在就在运行。
of code that's gonna use that
background data Run right now.
我们得告诉它什么时候逃跑
We got to tell it when to run,
我们必须依赖JavaScript，它知道后台工作何时完成
we got to rely on JavaScript that
knows when the background work is done
为了自动触发，函数在那个时刻运行。
to automatically trigger,
the function to Run on that moment.
这就是允许我们，人们，建立这些非阻塞，
This is what allows us, people,
to build these non-blocking,
动态、快速的应用程序。
dynamic, fast applications.
我们可以在后台设置大量的东西
We can handle setting up a ton
of stuff in the background
当我们在前台运行代码时，
while we race on in
the foreground running our code,
响应用户的交互，构建这些动态应用程序。
being responsive to users' interactions,
building these dynamic applications.
这就是真正使JavaScript非常、非常特殊和非常可用的地方。
This is what really makes JavaScript very,
very special and very usable.